Milne School; Records ua659
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1890-1977; 3; 12.0 cubic ft.
  - Social Studies Manual For Beginning Teachers, Snyder, Gerald, Undated (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Space, 1970-1971 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Space, Physical Plant, 1969-1970 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Space and Schedule Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Spanish Club, 1971 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Speech Contest -Robert circa Pruyn Medal, 1917-1919; 1921; 1925-1928 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Spring Concert, 1948 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Sports Night, 1950-1964 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Staff, 1949-1960 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Staff, 1968-1969 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Staff, 1969-1970 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Staff, 1970-1971 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Staff, 1971-1972 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Staff, 1972-1973 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Staff List, 1969-1973 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Staff Loads, 1949-1952 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Staff Needs, 1963-1966 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Staff Promotions, 1970-1971 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Staff Promotions, 1971-1972 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Staff Recruiting Materials, 1951-1958 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Staff References and Correspondence, 1949-1972 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Staff, Resigned, Retired, 1965-1969 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - State College Summer Session, 1931 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - State College For Teachers -19 English Curriculum (Tentative), 1950 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - State Department Annual Statistical Reports, 1941-1960 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - State Department of Education, Board of Trustees, Annual Reports, 1935-1942 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - State Department of Education, Curriculum Offerings Report, 1951-1952 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - State Department of Education, Enrollment by Subjects Report, 1937 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - State Department of Education, Homemaking Department Annual Reports, 1948-1958 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - State Department of Education, Library Report, 1933-1942 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - State Department of Education, School Library Report, 1935-1960 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - State Department of Education, Secondary School Report, 1931-1960 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - State Department of Education, Secondary School Report, 1966-1970 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Student Association Funds, 1969-1972 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Student Association Policies, 1969 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Student Handbook, "Bear Facts", 1966-1967 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Student Memorandums on Disciplinary Action, 1950 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Student Roster, 1967-1968 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Student Teacher Handbook, 1970-1971 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Student Teacher Handbook, 1971-1972 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Student Teacher Handbook and Materials, 1969-1971 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Student Teachers, 1969-1970 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Student Teachers, 1970-1971 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Student Teaching, 1971-1972 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Student Teaching-Data, 1966-1972 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Student Teaching Policies, 1953-1961 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Study Habits -Study Halls and Study Improvement Clippings, 1949; 1950; 1959 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Summer Orientation Program Final Report, 1964 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Summer Orientation Program, 1969 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Summer School, 1960 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Summer School, 1961 (Box 14 (3-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Summer School, 1962 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Summer School, 1963 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Summer School, 1964 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Summer School, 1965 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Summer School, 1966 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Summer School, 1967 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Summer School, 1968 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Summer School, 1969 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - SUNYA-Class of 1966-Follow-up Study, 1967-1970 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - SUNYA-Class of 1967-Follow-up Study, 1968-1969 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - SUNYA-Class of 1968-Follow-up Study, 1969 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - SUNYA Class of 1969-Follow-up Study, 1970 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - SUNYA Courses for Milne Students, 1957-1970 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - SUNYA Experimental College, 1968 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - SUNYA Graduates Follow-up Study, 1967-1968 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - SUNYA Graduates Follow-up Study, 1969-1970 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - SUNYA-Milne Memos, 1967; 1971 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - SUNYA - New Patterns of Undergraduate Education, 1968 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - SUNYA Personnel Policies, 1953-1967 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - SUNYA Reports - Campus Schools, 1968-1971 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Supervisor's Schedule, 1969-1970 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Supervisor's Schedule of Duties, 1970-1971 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Survey of Milne Graduates, 1948-1949 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Symposium-SUNY, 1951 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Symposium-SUNY, 1954 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Taft, Robert E. Memorial Award and the Ruth E. Wesley Memorial Award, 1944-1972 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Teacher Education Committee, 1968 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Teacher Education Committee, 1969 Teacher Education Demonstration Class, 1970 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Teacher Effectiveness-Another Approach, 1965 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Teacher Evaluation Report and Forms, 1971 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Teacher Loads, 1974-1975 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Teacher Satisfactions and Dissatisfactions, 1954 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Teachers, Student-Meetings with, 1964-1965 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Teaching, Student Guides, 1954-1967 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Teaching, Student Off Campus, 1956-1959 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Teaching, Student Seminar Materials, 1952-1970 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Teaching, Student Success Prediction Stud, 1958-1969 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Television, Closed Circuit, 1953-1959 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Television, Educational, 1952-1964 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Testing Program -19 Materials, 1947-1966 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Theater, ca. 1960 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Tuition, 1945-1946; 1971-1972 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Usage of Milne for SUNYA Students, 1972 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Vault, 1929 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Visitors - Professional, 1963 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - War Memorial Service, 1948 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Workshop, Buffalo, 1950 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Workshop, College Faculty-Canton, N.Y., 1942 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Workshop, Plattsburgh, 1957 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Workshop, Potsdam, 1954 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Workshop, Principals at Colgate, 1960 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Year - School Calendar, 1958-1970 (Box 15 (3-Subject Files), Folder 52)
- Principal's Correspondence Files, 1952-1973; 4; 3.33 cubic ft.
  Materials are arranged alphabetically.
  Contains correspondence, memoranda, reports, and other data. Alphabetical subject files from the post Fossieck years to the closing of Milne in 1977.
  - Activities Suggestions, 1976-1977 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 1)
  - Activity Period Schedule, 1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 2)
  - Administrative Account, 1976-1977 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 3)
  - Admission, 1973 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 4)
  - Admission, 1973-1974 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 5)
  - Admission, 1974-1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 6)
  - Admission, 1975-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 7)
  - Admissions Committee, 1974 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 8)
  - Admissions Material, ca. 1970 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 9)
  - Advisory Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 10)
  - Alma Mater Poem, Undated (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 11)
  - Alumni Ball, 1975-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 12)
  - Alumni Ball, 1977 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 13)
  - Annual Report of Characteristics of Student Population, 1973 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 14)
  - "Answers Please", 1975-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 15)
  - Apprenticeship Program (Teacher Training), 1972-1973 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 16)
  - Aptitude Testing (See Confidential Series), 1930-1977 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 17)
  - Assemblies, 1972 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 18)
  - Assemblies, 1972-1973 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 19)
  - Assembly Programs, 1974-1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 20)
  - Assembly Programs, 1975-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 21)
  - Athletics, 1972-1973 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 22)
  - Attendance Policy, 1974-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 23)
  - Attendance Report, 1976-1977 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 24)
  - Attendance Report - Bureau of Non-Public Schools, 1977 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 25)
  - Audio Visual Equipment, 1972 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 26)
  - Audio Visual Inventory Sheets, 1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 27)
  - Awards Assembly, 1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 28)
  - Awards - Bausch & Lomb Science Award, 1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 29)
  - Barsam, J. J. - Memorial Fund, 1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 30)
  - Baseball Schedule, 1974-1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 31)
  - Baseball Schedule, 1975-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 32)
  - Basic Educational Data System (BEDS) Report - Non-Public Schools, 1974-1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 33)
  - Basic Educational Data System (BEDS) Report - Non-Public Schools, 1975-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 34)
  - Basic Educational Data System (BEDS) Report - Non-Public Schools, 1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 35)
  - Basketball, 1975-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 36)
  - Basketball Chaperones, 1974-1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 37)
  - Basketball Rules, Schedules, 1974 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 38)
  - Book Inventory, 1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 39)
  - "Buckley Amendment", Rights and Privacy Act, 1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 40)
  - Budget Expenditures, 1972-1973 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 41)
  - Budget Information, 1972-1974 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 42)
  - Budget Record, 1972-1973 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 43)
  - Building Utilization, 1972-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 44)
  - Bureau of Child Accounting and Guidance, 1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 45)
  - Business Course Descriptions, 1975-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 46)
  - Cafeteria Evaluation, 1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 47)
  - Calendar, 1972-1973 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 48)
  - Calendar, 1973-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 49)
  - Calendar, 1975-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 50)
  - Calendar, 1972-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 51)
  - Campus School Operation, 1974-1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 52)
  - Campus School Report, 1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 53)
  - Campus School/SUNY, 1974 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 54)
  - Campus University Lab School (CULS), Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 55)
  - Center for Counseling and Research, 1973 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 56)
  - Central Hudson Valley League - Sports, 1973-1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 57)
  - Class Activites, 1972-1973 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 58)
  - Class Cuts, 1972-1973 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 59)
  - Class Roster, 1974-1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 60)
  - Class Roster, 1975-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 61)
  - Clinical School, 1974-1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 62)
  - Commencement Programs, 1974-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 63)
  - Committee on the Future of Milne, 1974 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 64)
  - Community Service, 1974-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 65)
  - Conduct Code, 1973 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 66)
  - "Convocation 70", 1970 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 67)
  - Cooperative Centers for Individual Development, 1973-1974 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 68)
  - Course Descriptions, 1970s (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 69)
  - Course Fee Requests, 1974-1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 70)
  - Course Fee Requests, 1975-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 71)
  - Course Guide, 1973-1974 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 72)
  - Course Offerings, 1975-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 73)
  - Courses, Descriptions, Schedules, 1976-1977 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 74)
  - Courses of Study, 1975-1976 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 75)
  - Curriculum, 1971-1972 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 76)
  - Curriculum, 1972-1973 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 77)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 78)
  - Curriculum Handbook, 1973-1974 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 79)
  - Daily Bulletins, 1974 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 80)
  - Daily Bulletins, 1975 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 81)
  - Daily Office Memos, 1975-1977 (Box 16 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 82)
  - Deans Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 1)
  - Description Profile, 1973-1974 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 2)
  - Directory, 1976-1977 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 3)
  - Disposition of Records - Milne School Files, 1972-1975 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 4)
  - Driver Education, 1972 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 5)
  - Driver Education, 1973-1974 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 6)
  - Education Department Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 7)
  - English Course Descriptions, 1975-1976 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 8)
  - Faculty Academic Ranks, 1973 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 9)
  - Faculty Directory, 1972-1975 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 10)
  - Faculty Evaluation Forms, 1975-1976 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 11)
  - Faculty Job Descriptions, 1970s (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 12)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 13)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 14)
  - Faculty Memos, 1974-1975 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 15)
  - Faculty Memos, 1975-1976 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 16)
  - Faculty Teaching Schedule - Classroom Usage, 1975 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 17)
  - Fashion Show, 1976 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 18)
  - Finances, 1976 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 19)
  - Fire Drills, 1967-1976 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 20)
  - First Day Materials, 1976-1977 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 21)
  - Grade 9 Team, 1973-1974 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 22)
  - Graduation, 1974 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 23)
  - Graduation, 1975 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 24)
  - Graduation, 1976 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 25)
  - Graduation, 1977 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 26)
  - Graduation, Requirements, 1975 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 27)
  - Guidance Materials, 1972-1973 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 28)
  - Historic Albany Pageant, 1922 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 29)
  - Homeroom Lists, 1974-1975 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 30)
  - Honors Assembly, 1975 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 31)
  - Interscholastic/School Activities, 1975-1977 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 32)
  - Inventory, 1975-1977 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 33)
  - Joint Code of Ethics, ca. 1970 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 34)
  - Lab Schools Analysis (not Milne), 1975 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 35)
  - Languages, Course Descriptions, 1975-1976 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 36)
  - Lawsuits Against Milne, 1971-1973 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 37)
  - Learning Center Calendars, 1975-1977 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 38)
  - Learning Center in Math and Language, 1974-1975 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 39)
  - Learning Labs, 1974-1975 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 40)
  - Legislature, 1971-1972 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 41)
  - Letters, 1976-1977 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 42)
  - Library Fund, 1969-1975 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 43)
  - Local Requirements for Milne Graduates, 1975 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 44)
  - Lunchroom Duty, 1975 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 45)
  - Luzinski, Stephen VS State of New York, 1974-1976 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 46)
  - Maps of Milne, 1970s (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 47)
  - Master Schedules, 1974-1975 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 48)
  - Master Schedules, 1975-1976 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 49)
  - Math/Science Course Descriptions Including Health, 1975-1976 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 50)
  - Methods Participation, 1972-1973 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 51)
  - Methods Participation, 1975 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 52)
  - Methods Program, 1974 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 53)
  - Methods Program, 1975-1976 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 54)
  - Mexico, 1972 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 55)
  - Mini-course Proposals, 1972 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 56)
  - Mini Mester, 1972 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 57)
  - Mini Mester, 1972-1973 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 58)
  - Mini Mester, 1976 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 59)
  - Mini Mester-Easter, 1972 (Box 17 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 60)
  - Mini Mester Evaluation, 1972 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 1)
  - Mini Mester, Faculty Meetings and Committees, 1972 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 2)
  - Mini Mester/Miscellaneous Subjects, 1972 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 3)
  - Mini Mester Proposal, 1972 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 4)
  - Mini Mester - Students, 1972 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 5)
  - Music, 1971-1972 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 6)
  - Music Equipment Inventory, 1974-1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 7)
  - National Education Association (NEA) Code of Ethics, 1970s (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 8)
  - National Honor Society, 1962-1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 9)
  - National Honor Society - Induction Ceremony, 1976 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 10)
  - Nonpublic School Attendance Report, 1974-1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 11)
  - Nonpublic School Attendance Report, 1975-1976 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 12)
  - Opening Day, 1972 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 13)
  - Opening Day Procedures, 1972-1973 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 14)
  - Opening Day Procedures, 1973-1974 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 15)
  - Parent's Association, 1971-1972 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 16)
  - Parent's Association, 1972-1973 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 17)
  - Parent's, Letters to, 1970-1972 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 18)
  - Parent's, Letters to, 1972-1973 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 19)
  - Parent's, Letters to, 1973-1976 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 20)
  - Parent's Night, 1967-1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 21)
  - "Phase Out" article in Tower Tribune, Undated (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 22)
  - Phi Delta Kappan, 1972-1973 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 23)
  - Planning/Annual Report, 1976 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 24)
  - Profile, 1973-1974 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 25)